So as I mentioned, there's a lot of the ecosystem out there
waiting for you.
Going past view, when you start looking at things
like server-side rendering, or you
want a higher meta framework that provides more built-in things,
highly recommend checking out Nux 3.
That should be coming close to stable soon.
But we have a Nux 3 Foundations workshop
that I actually gave recently.
So if you check that out, that'll also
walk you through how Nux 3 works.
And with a new View 3 knowledge, you'll
be able to pair those things pretty well.
In addition, whether it's TypeScript as well, TypeScript,
be sure to check those things out.
Because with View 3, TypeScript is much easier,
especially for those using Composition API.
And so other than that, I would say,
I think that about wraps it up from my end.
So a big thanks to everyone on the team here
from Frontend Masters for hosting this.
But for those online, if you have any questions,
I'm online in the community under the moniker Ben Codesen.
So there's my info there.
So if you ever want to reach out, have any questions,
I don't hesitate to do so.
Thanks.
Thank you.